Guide to the Hasia Diner Papers, 1970-2012 MC.153
New York University Archives
- Series I: Research Notes, 20561
  - Subseries G: We Remember with Reverance and Love, 238970
    - B'nai Brith, undated; 240940 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - B'hai B'rith Waukesha, undated; 240941 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Rabbi Isadore Breslau, undated; 240942 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Busker, undated; 240943 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Subseries H. Roads Taken
    - Roads Taken Research: Author's Last Name A-D, 1986-2012 (Box 25)
    - Roads Taken Research: Author's Last Name D-H, 1986-2012 (Box 26)
    - Roads Taken Research: Author's Last Name H-L, 1986-2012 (Box 27)
    - Roads Taken Research: Author's Last Name L-N, 1986-2012 (Box 28)
    - Roads Taken Research: Author's Last Name N-R, 1986-2012 (Box 29)
    - Roads Taken Research: Author's Last Name R-Z and Author Not Listed, 1986-2012 (Box 30)
    - Roads Taken Research: No Author Listed, Images, 1986-2012 (Box 31)
    - Roads Taken Research Notes, 1986-2012 (Box 32)
    - Roads Taken Unpublished Draft, 1986-2012 (Box 33)